Welcome to pioneer u plus
The application where you can
learn many thing related to IT
Our applicaion provide many
guided tutorial which you are interested in
First click on tutorial
Next, click on the tutorial
you are interested in
Lastly, see which topic you
are interested
After selecting the topic
It will provide you will
a step by step video tutorial
With subtitle you have selected
After you are done
with the video
Click next
It will bring you to a
simulation game
Where you can test your skill
from the video you have watch
In the simulation game
You are able to earn
point which can redeem
So let go back to the
menu
Click on redeem
It will show you the
point you have
and click redeem now
It will provide you a list
of wonder prize
Our app also have leaderboard
Where you can see you
and your friend
So let click on leaderboard
As you can see, you are 4th
among your freinds
Lastly
You can change the
word size,
color and language
in the setting
by click on setting in the menu
This is the end of this video
please enjoy the
application